So now we have our simple storage. That's all compiled,
现在我们已经把 "SimpleStorage" 编译好了
let's learn how we can actually deploy this thing.
现在我们来学习一下如何部署它
Remember, in remix, we actually deployed it to one of two different places,
在 Remix 里，其实我们可以把它部署到两个不同的地方
we deployed it to either a JavaScript VM,
我们可以把它部署到 "JavaScript VM"
or with our injected web three, with our Metamask.
或是 "Injected Web3" ，也就是 Metamask 上
Let's learn first ad, do the JavaScript VM.
我们先来学习怎么部署到 "JavaScript VM" 上
And then we'll learn how to use the injected web three,
之后再学习如何部署到 "Injected Web3" 上
or a meta mask or some connection to an actual test net.
也可以说是 Metamask 或者任何真实的测试网络上
So in order to deploy this to a JavaScript virtual invite I'm in or kind of a fake blockchain,
为了部署这个到 JavaScript 虚拟机环境或者说假的区块链上
we're gonna need to get a fake blockchain.
我们需要先拥有一个假的区块链
Now in the future, we're going to be using the Hardhead runtime environment
未来，我们将会使用 Hardhat 运行环境
as our JavaScript virtual machine or aka our fake blockchain.
作为我们的 JavaScript 虚拟机或者说假的区块链
But for this section, I want us to use a tool called ganache.
但在本节中，我想用的是一个叫做 "Ganache" 的工具
There's a link to this in the GitHub repository.
可以通过 GitHub 仓库中的链接跳转到这里
Ganache is similar to a virtual machine in remix.
Ganache 和 Remix 里的虚拟机很相似
It's a fake blockchain that we can run locally
这是一个我们可以在本地运行的假区块链
to actually test, deploy and run code.
可以供我们进行测试，部署还有运行代码
It's also a nice way to see things that are going on in a blockchain.
这也是观察区块链上正在发生的事情的一个好方法。
Let's go ahead and spin up the ganache application after you install it,
你需要先安装 Ganache 然后我们就可以启动它了
the ganache application will look a little something like this.
应用程序 Ganache 看起来就是这样的
And to spin up a fake blockchain really quickly, ou can just go ahead and click Quickstart.
用它启动一个假区块链真的很快，你只需要点击一下 "QUICKSTART"
This will spin up a fake blockchain that's running locally on your computer right here, which is fantastic.
它就会在你的计算机本地启动一个假区块链，真是太酷了
It comes with a whole bunch of fake accounts
它带有一大堆假账户
exactly like how remix comes with a ton of fake accounts with 100 ether each
就和 Remix 上每个带有 100 ETH 的假账户完全一样
ganache comes with a bunch of fake accounts with 100 ether each.
Ganache 同样的带有一大堆假账户并且每个也有 100 ETH
They also come with the private keys
它们还附有私钥
that we can use in our applications to actually take control of these fake accounts.
这可以让我们在应用程序中控制这些假账户
Remember, don't use these private keys on a public blockchain.
记住，不要在公共区块链上使用这些私钥
They're for development purposes only
它们仅用于开发目的
because a lot of people know these private keys
因为很多人都知道这些私钥
in our code. One of the first things that we're going to need to do
在我们的代码中，我们首先要做的就是
is actually connect to our blockchain
连接到我们的区块链上
remix does this a little bit behind the scenes,
Remix 在幕后完成了这一工作
if we're choosing JavaScript virtual machine
如果我们选择 JavaScript 虚拟机
remix chooses its own fake blockchain that it runs.
Remix 就会选择它自己运行的假区块链
If we choose injected web three, as we know, meta mask pops up,
如果我们选择了 "Injected Web3"，如我们所料 Metamask 弹了出来
and it connects to our meta mask,
它连接到了我们的 Metamask 上
this connection that remix does, is actually doing something really interesting.
Remix 所做的这种连接，其实是一件很有意思的事
It's not just connecting to our meta mask by some magical powers.
它不是通过某种魔法力量连接到了我们的 Metamask
It's actually connecting to our meta mask, which has a connection to the blockchain behind the scenes.
而是通过在幕后与区块链连接从而连接到了我们的 Metamask
If you open up your meta mask,
如果你打开 Metamask
and you go down to you select the networks and you select ad networks,
然后打开网络选项("Networks")选择添加网络("Add Network")
you'll get popped up into a UI that looks like this.
就会弹出一个像是这样的 UI 界面
If we go back and hit select networks over here,
如果你点击这里返回到“网络”("Networks")选项界面
we can actually see information about these different networks.
我们就可以看到这些不同网络的一系列信息
One of the main things that we can see
我们能看到的主要内容之一是
is that all these networks have something called an RPC URL.
所有网络都有一个叫做 "RPC URL" 的东西
RPC stands for remote procedure call.
RPC 表示“远程过程调用”("Remote Procedure call")
And then URL is uniform resource locator.
而 URL 则是“统一资源定位符”("Uniform Resource Locator")
This RPC URL stands for a connection to a blockchain node that somebody is running
这个 "RPC URL" 代表，到某人正在运行的区块链节点("Blockchain node")的连接
this this URL connects us to make API calls and to interact with a blockchain node.
这个 URL 连接我们进行 API 的调用以及与区块链节点的交互
Blockchain nodes run with software, and some of them expose an API call.
区块链节点使用软件运行，其中的一些会公开 API 调用
If you look at the NGO Aetherium website, there actually are instructions
for you to run your own blockchain node for a real
blockchain like Aetherium. Most of these have flags like dash
HTTP dot ADR to expose these RPC endpoints. So if you ever want
to run your own node, your own real blockchain node, instead of
using meta masks or any other the providers that we're going
to go through, you can use go Aetherium, or whatever
blockchain you're working with software to run your own notes.
But it's this RPC URL that allows us to connect to Rinkeby,
if on Rinkeby ropsten, if we're on ropsten main net if we're on
Main net, etc. And it's going to be the way that we're going to
connect to our ganache blockchain that we're running
inside of this application. So if you look at the top of your
ganache here, there's a section called the RPC server. And this
is the endpoint of our ganache node right now. So what we can
do is we can copy this and go back to our VS code, and paste
it in here to see if we can connect instead of HTTP. With
these capitals, we're gonna have a B lowercase instead of the
uppercase, because the lowercase is more correct, and it looks
nicer. But now we have the endpoint. Hypothetically, with
just this, we can start making calls and API calls to this
endpoint, go to this JSON RPC specification. Again, link will
be in the GitHub repo, we can actually see different calls we
can make directly to our node to get different information. eath
get blocked by hash eath get blocked by number. And all of
these wonderful pieces in here. Making these API calls directly
is is a little bit annoying to do ourselves. If you want to do
it yourself, you absolutely can using an API endpoint like Axios
or fetch. However, we're going to use a rapper to interact with
our node and do things like deploy and interact and other
such things with our blockchain node. This is finally where
ethers comes
into play.